<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MB Blog</title>
    <link>https://michaelburghall.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MB Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2008–2018, Steve Francia and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 20:24:16 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://michaelburghall.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Convert Azure tags in Power BI</title>
      <link>https://michaelburghall.com/post/convert_azure_tags_in_power_bi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 20:24:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelburghall.com/post/convert_azure_tags_in_power_bi/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;p&gt;If you are using Power BI and pulling data from Azure Cost Management you will most likely want to extract data from tags created within Azure. This isn&#39;t as easy as it seems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://michaelburghall.com/static/power_bi/Edit_Query.PNG&#34; alt=&#34;Edit Query&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Importance of Calling</title>
      <link>https://michaelburghall.com/post/the_importance_of_calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 00:29:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://michaelburghall.com/post/the_importance_of_calling/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;p&gt;Firstly, what do I mean by &#39;The Importance of Calling&#39; - this is simply the action of picking up the phone, hitting call on Slack, Teams or whatever is your flavour and speaking to people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This always sounds so simple and I debated whether it made a good post - but so many times have I come across chains of emails or messages trying to achieve something like resolve a technical issue or clarify a point. I always find just hitting call and speaking cuts down all the noise and resolves the issue in far less time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So often people send an email and push the problem to someone else or delay it, but this doesn&#39;t gain anything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When asked people often people say &#39;I sent an email because I needed it documented&#39;, but if you get something resolved or agreed asap, then you can capture it and document it after speaking to someone and send &#39;that email&#39; as confirmation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Try it the next time you&#39;re going to type an email and see the results for yourself!&lt;/p&gt;

        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
